In this house there is a presence.
Presence is a horror, thriller, drama film directed by Steven Soderbergh.
A couple and their children move into a seemingly normal suburban home.
When strange events occur, they begin to believe there is
something else in the house with them.
The presence is about to disrupt their lives in unimaginable ways.
Chloe, played by Callina Liang.
Rebekah, played by Lucy Liu.
Chris, played by Chris Sullivan.
Tyler, played by Eddy Maday.
Ryan, played by West Mulholland.
Cece, played by Julia Fox.
Presence is a 2024 American supernatural thriller drama film
directed by Steven Soderbergh and written by David Koepp.
It stars Lucy Liu, Chris Sullivan, Callina Liang, Eddy
Maday, West Mulholland, and Julia Fox.
Presence premiered at the Sundance Film Festival on January 19, 2024.
It was released in U.S.
theaters by Neon on January 24, 2025.
The film has grossed $11.1 million on a $2 million production
budget, and received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship, new
jersey, haunted house, grief, interracial marriage.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.